Office of the Vice-President, University Services fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Assistant to Vice-President, University Services, 1971 - 1975; F-207-5; 37 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Ian Kelsey and William (Bill) Stewart as the Assistant to Vice-President, University Services and their liaison with university services staff, departments, and committees on campus. For a list of the departments and committees, see Access Points below. Records also consist of evaluation forms used by Counsellors; a financial aid study; budget development; reports on and planning for highschool and college recruiting visits; correspondence regarding handicapped students, rotunda renovations, student employment, orientation and workshops; and policy development. Records include correspondence and working papers, financial statements, agendas and minutes, reports, surveys and publications.
  The University Presidents' Council; Day Care Advisory Committee; CUSO; Interfaith Centre; School for the Contemporary Arts; Canadian Association of University and College Student Services; Daycare Centre; Centre for Students with Disabilities; Reading and Study Centre; Simon Fraser University Staff Association; Staff Relations Advisory Council; Simon Fraser Student Society; School for the Contemporary Arts; Residence and Housing Office; Health, Counselling and Career Centre; C.K.S.F. Radio; Canada Manpower
  For records relating to William (Bill) Stewart as Director of Student Services from 1977 to 1996 see F-107-3.
  - Correspondence, 1971; F-207-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-34.
  - School and College Liaison, 1971; F-207-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-38.
  - Faculty/Advisor Visits to Schools and Colleges, 1971 - 1972; F-207-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-39.
  - Financial Aid Study, 1971 - 1972; F-207-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-56.
  - General, vol. 1, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-59.
  - General, vol. 2, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-60.
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-61.
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-62.
  - Tri-Universities Meetings, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-40.
  - Evaluation Forms - Counsellors, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-33.
  - Day Care Advisory Committee, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 207-12)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-37.
  - Applications for Day Care Executive, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-57.
  - Report on School and College Liaison, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-22.
  - School Visits, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-58.
  - College Visits, 1972; F-207-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-32.
  - CUSO Correspondence, 1972 - 1973; F-207-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-5.
  - University Services Support Staff Meetings, 1972 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-47.
  - Student Services, 1972 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-1.
  - Correspondence, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-41.
  - Policies and Philosophy, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-46.
  - Chaplain's Office, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-63.
  - Attrition Committee, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-44.
  - Arts Centre, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-43.
  - Budget, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-42.
  - Counsellors' Conference, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-4.
  - College Visits, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-3.
  - Report on School and College Liaison, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-21.
  - CACUSS Correspondence, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-8.
  - Day Care, 1973; F-207-5-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-23.
  - Handicapped Students, 1973 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-24.
  - Rotunda Renovation, 1973 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-19.
  - Reading and Study Centre, 1973 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-20.
  - Simon Fraser Staff Association, 1973 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-50.
  - Staff Relations Advisory Council, 1973 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 207-13)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-49.
  - CACUSS Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-207-5-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-9.
  - Correspondence, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-12.
  - University Services Group Meetings, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-45.
  - Staff Relations Advisory Council, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-48.
  - Student Employment 'Experience 74' Project, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-53.
  - Student Activity Fees, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-52.
  - Student Society, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-51.
  - Student Employment, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-54.
  - CC and A Correspondence, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-6.
  - Theatre, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-7.
  - Residences, vol. 1, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-17.
  - Residences, vol. 2, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-18.
  - Counselling, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-16.
  - Co-op Radio, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-15.
  - Canada Manpower Centre, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-14.
  - Campus Life Proposal, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-13.
  - NWCPA Correspondence, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-11.
  - CACUSS Correspondence, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-10.
  - Confidentiality of Student Records, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-30.
  - Open House, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-26.
  - Job Evaluation Committee, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-25.
  - Residences - Pet Problem, 1974; F-207-5-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-31.
  - Orientation, 1974 - 1975; F-207-5-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-27.
  - Options for the Future Seminar, 1975; F-207-5-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 207-14)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-2-0-0-29.